Kouban
High
School
Welcome
New
Students
How about tennis? You interested?
Bulletin Board
Soccer Club     Baseball Club                  Soft Tennis Club now recruiting!
Concert Band   Drama Club          Kendo Club
Hey!
Okay, right over here.
Did I take a wrong turn?
Excuse me!
Do you know where the room
for the drama club is?
You a new student?
Yes.
Perfect, I happen to be the club's pres...
President! Kitahama Eiji.
Well, I'm Nanakura Rin.
Sorry to spring this on you
when you were hoping to sign up, but...
I'm the only member at the moment.
It'd be great if you joined,
but no pressure, okay?
Okay! Sure...
Wow, it's like in
"The Beginning of a Story."
Anyway, the club room is this way.
Okay.
Well, welcome to Drama!
Prez! We got a new recruit, apparently.
I thought you were the president.
Eiji... were you messing around, again?
Surprise!
Whacha think? Just like in
"The Beginning of a Story", wasn't it?
He seems kind of weird...
So you're looking to join?
Oh, yes! I'm interested in acting.
Could you try reading this bit, then?
R-Right now?
Yes! Okay, let's begin.
O, speak again, bright angel, for thou art as
glorious to this night, being o’er my head,
as is a winged messenger of heaven!
There he goes again...
Go on, it's your line now. Come on!
O Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name,
and I'll no longer be a Capulet.
Well...?
Yep, Romeo here!
What are you doing, President?
I mean, she kind of bowled me over...
Uh, what was your name?
It's Nanakura Rin.
Nanakura-san, we'd love
to have you join the club.
Yes! Thank you so much!
Why's she thanking him?
We're glad to have you!
That was pretty impressive just now.
It was fantastic!
Episode 1        The Beginning of a Story?
Bring it!
Nice kill!
The truth is, all guys wish they could
be popular at least once in life.
You're actually interested
in romance, senpai?
Wow, rude!
Even I dream about having a harem, y'know.
A harem...?
Maybe I should take you out
for a date sometime, then.
What brought that on?
I-It was acting! I was teasing you
like one of those impish girls do.
Are you acting out a simulated
harem experience, all for me?!
Aw, you're a real sweetheart!
I-It's not like I was
doing it for your sake!
Your imp act is good,
but it's hard to say no to a tsundere.
I don't know if I'd be able to choose!
Now I know how tough
having a harem would actually be.
You've got real acting chops.
I like acting around you
for some reason, Senpai.
Wait, are you acting now? Or...?
I-It was acting, of course!
Sorry, sorry.
But that was the cutest of all!
It was...?
Kouban
Private
High
School
That's not gonna work.
I'm about the only girl who'd
approach someone making that face.
So going for the "taciturn, cool guy who
handles large props" approach won't work?
I think it might be effective
if I mastered it.
Gimme some tips, here!
Think about the emotional side more.
That's what I was going for!
How come it's so different when you do it?
Is it in the eyes?
The quiet act...
It's kind of hard to learn anything
without words, though.
I don't care.
Cool act!
S-Something like that, maybe?
I see what you mean.
I don't know if I can pull that off.
I like talking too much.
I'm probably always
going to be like this, huh?
What's so funny?
It's a secret!
Man, I have no idea what I'm doing.
Senpai, you could take
a break during lunch, you know.
I have to finish these
before the culture festival.
We're desperate for all the help we can get!
I might shrivel up at this rate.
Even though my whole plan
was to be a buff stagehand!
S-Since there's no other choice,
I'll have to feed you.
Getting fed by Tsundere-chan?!
You sure you're not spoiling me?
I'll die tomorrow
from the luck backlash!
Eat mine, too.
There's no way I deserve
to be fed by Cool-chan!
I'd be locked in for death!
By the way, we happen to have this prop...
Could you lend... a paw, maybe?
Sorry...
M-Meow...
Okay! I don't care if I die now!
I can't believe you can even act like a cat!
I'm actually too embarrassed
to perform right now.
I've got it!
Huh... wait.
My phone's missing.
Did you lose it?
And I was gonna take a picture
of Rin-chan in those cat ears.
This is weird...
If I call his phone to make it ring,
I can use that as an excuse
to get his number!
Senpai!
I... I-I-I...
What? What is it?
What?
I guess I could call your number,
but then you'd have mine, wouldn't you?
Quit playing around and help me, please!
You can have the number, so just call it!
I'm begging you!
I dunno, should I?
Aw, fine. It's okay if you don't want it.
Oh no! I was a little too impish!
Maybe I could ask Tsundere-chan?
H-Hurry up and tell me!
I'll call your phone, but this
is a one-time-only deal, got it?!
That's my Tsundere-chan.
So understanding. Thank you.
I should probably thank
you too, Tsundere-chan.
There it is.
Found it!
That's great.
Hello?
Hello? Senpai, what is it?
Oh, nothing big,
I just wanted to thank you.
I appreciate you helping me find my phone.
That's the kind of call you
usually make in the evening, Senpai.
Huh?
Are you the only one around, Senpai?
Yeah, everyone else is in the gymnasium.
I see.
Hey, Senpai...
Could you help me out with this art project?
You're good with that sort of thing, right?
Could you...?
Is that really how you ask someone for help?
S-Sorry!
Um, w-what should I do?
I'm begging you, ask as Cool-chan this time!
You're the only one I can turn to.
I-I guess I better help then!
What do you need to know?
He looks like he's having fun.
It's from Romeo and Juliet.
And this is...
What is it?
Romeo and Juliet.
I wasn't sure how to get
the colors right for sunset...
That's your concern?
Why try such a complicated picture?
Aw, but I don't know anything about art!
You're such a good artist,
it'd be great if you did it!
Who was that?!
It was... um... the spoiled girl...
That's one hell of a secret weapon!
I-It's my desperation move, so...
He redid all the colors for me.
And behind him was a woman standing
silently in a white kimono...
And at her feet... a massive swell of water!
Damn!
You're a pro at scary stories, Tsuu-chan.
I guess that's what being
a writer does for you.
You're the scariest one here, man.
Don't you agree...
Huh. You okay?
Dead
Remember to lock up, all right?
Sure!
Take care!
Sure...?
Can't believe it spooked you so bad
you're afraid to change on your own.
I-It's not like I was afraid or anything!
B-But keep talking to me! Okay?!
W-What is it, Senpai?!
The idea of Tsundere-chan being
scared has got me so hyped!
Is Spoiled-chan in there, too?!
I'm so scared!
You can't leave me alone, okay, Senpai?
You're going to break the door!
I kind of want to, just to see
what kind of face you're making!
Dammit!
Honestly...
Huh. I'm not scared anymore.
I don't suppose impish Rin-chan
is in there too, is she?!
I can't finish changing
if you keep interrupting me...
Pseudo Harem
Wow, I had no idea.
Excuse me...
What's up?
Is... Kitahama-senpai around?
Oh, Kitahama's napping over there.
Feel free to wake him.
We should go.
Sure.
Seeya, Rin-chan.
Bye!
Oh... have a nice day.
She's cute, isn't she?
More than Kitahama deserves.
Um, Senpai?
The club meeting's started...
If you don't wake up,
I'm gonna play a prank on you.
He really isn't waking up.
I really could play a prank on him!
No, no!
I need to stop thinking like Imp-chan.
You'd forgive me even if I did pull
a prank on you, right, Senpai?
I think a lack of response
makes this way more embarrassing.
Shoot, is it time for club already?
He almost saw me as Spoiled-chan!
That was a close one!
You went out of your way to get me?
Sorry about that...
Why are you holding my hand?
I-Imp-chan and the others
were playing a prank on you earlier!
Yeah.
They what?!
I'm going back to sleep.
Our drama club president's best...
Romeo face!
It's quite the face all right!
I've got it as my wallpaper,
but I'm kinda tired of it.
Could I trouble the drama club's rising star
for a picture with her cutest face?
I want a picture of you too, Senpai!
Perfect!
Wait, this looks different...
This is a special occasion, okay?!
And you better not take a weird picture!
What is going on here, rising star?
This is too much,
even as a favor to you, Senpai!
It's too embarrassing!
What're you two fooling around with?
Prez.
Nanakura's too embarrassed and
her expressions keep coming out weird.
What? That's no good.
Sorry....
Show her how it's done, Prez!
Very well then.
Full power!
I got it.
The rising star of the
drama club's golden smile.
Nice! Send it to me too, would you?
Please, don't!
How'd you do on midterms, anyway?
Decently, I think...
What about you, Senpai?
Senpai...?
I-If you insist! I'll show you! But this is a
special occasion! Don't ask again, got it?!
Tsundere-senpai?
Now it's your turn, Nanakura!
I have to show you mine?
It's called sharing the shame!
What are you talking about?
Can you keep a secret?
You seriously think I'd spill a secret
from Cool-chan without a fight?!
I'm not that stupid!
Those are some really bad math scores.
So are yours...
Imp-chan seems like she'd be
pretty calculating, though.
I wasn't paying attention in class so
I could get you to tutor me, Senpai.
Hell yeah!
I'm going to cram school starting tomorrow!
Time to get serious!
Cram school?!
Maybe I should study more, too...
Nah, you shouldn't change a thing, Nanakura.
I wanna get smart so I can teach you.
Math for Imp-chan,
Japanese history for Tsundere-chan,
science for Spoiled-chan,
and social studies for Cool-chan.
I'm just going to study instead!
Excuse me...?
I got into a cooking battle with Tsuu-chan
in our self studies period for home ec.
He's got the lead right now
with the Prez's vote, so...
We want you to vote too, Nanakura.
And we'll announce who made what
afterwards, to keep it impartial.
I'm not exactly a gourmet...
Just go with whichever you prefer.
Now, let the judging begin!
A tastes like it was made
according to the recipe,
but B has a bit of a twist to it...
Huh. Hang on.
If I choose whichever I like better,
and end up not choosing Senpai's cooking...
That'd be like saying
he's not to my liking?!
I have to guess which one is his!
No! I will guess correctly!
He doesn't seem the type to stick
to the recipe, so is it B?!
No, he might've followed
the directions to win the contest!
Senpai... Senpai would—
Nanakura—!
This is technically our lunch, so...
Now, which is it?!
B!
I like B more!
That's Eiji's cooking!
Yay!
Uh, shouldn't I be celebrating?
I guess it's a draw.
And we're out of people to ask.
Sorry...
Now, hang on, what
if we got Spoiled-chan to vote?
I can't do that embarrassing
act in front of actual people!
Aren't I a person?
Look, I just can't!
But everyone would be so impressed!
No!
Who's Spoiled-chan?
Kind of... a little act that
Nanakura puts on sometimes.
I see.
Hey, what if I treat you to lunch?
I already ate!
Have you decided what to wear
for the inter-club relay race yet, Senpai?
Two days until
the sports festival
I've got it!
This is definitely the one.
Don't you think it'd be perfect?
On Tsundere-chan!
Excuse me?
I think dressing like a princess
is a natural fit for a tsundere...
And then Cool-chan in Japanese clothes.
As for Imp-chan...
Senpai, I'd be running
the race by myself in that case.
And?
Please, just pick one!
You mean I have to choose?!
Only one... only one...?
What about the real me, then?
Gotta be loungewear!
Loungewear?!
But it's supposed to be a costume...
Loungewear or nothing!
I've always wondered what
actresses wear at home!
But... it's just normal t-shirts and stuff.
Nothing worth showing off.
Like that? Or that? Maybe that... or this?
Yeah, loungewear it is!
No.
Am I trying too hard with the hair?
I wonder what Senpai will think.
Nanakura?
Oh, Senpai, good mor—
Whoa, what happened to your head?!
Follicle                                         Disaster
I should be asking you!
Man, you look good no matter
how you do your hair, Imp-chan.
Maybe I should do my hair
how you like it next, Senp...
I'm sorry, I have to know
what caused that bedhead.
You look good no matter how you do
your hair, Spoiled-chan!
I'm sorry, I have to know
what caused that bedhead!
Well, I wasn't expecting you
to be showing your forehead off!
If I had known I would've fixed my hair,
even if it made me late!
I can't believe my idiotic bedhead
is stealing your amazing forehead gag!
I'm so sorry!
It's... not a gag, though.
Man, I've got no appeal
and no smoothness at all.
That's what happens when you oversleep.
You were running through my thoughts,
so I couldn't sleep at night!
Don't try to be smooth
with your hair like that, please!
Hey, making you smile
is enough to satisfy me.
Cut it out!
Romeo, just call me Romeo.
But you're not Romeo?
So cold...
I-I only did it because I'm not cold!
And I can't have you getting sick.
I'm so psyched up
that I'm feeling warmer now!
If you get sick, I'll take care of you.
That's the kinda thing I oughta be saying...
It'd definitely get me girls.
All right, back to the grind.
Maybe I should dress lighter tomorrow...
T-Twelve?!
Tomorrow's Weather
Cloudy
I'll have to hang in there tomorrow.